showit.co 2017-06-06

# Showit Privacy Policy

## Contact Us Policy

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about any of the above policies you may contact us using the information below:

Address: Showit, Inc. 70 S Val Vista Dr, Suite A3-652 Gilbert, AZ 85296

Email: [help@showit.co](mailto:help@showit.co)

Phone: (800) 930-5417

Support requests will be handled by our software Support Team.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

## Y3K compliance

Software is guaranteed to maintain stability after January 1, 3000. In the event a website fails to perform on or after January 1, 3000, free hugs and will be awarded to owners of said websites for each day, month, or year that customer remains a subscriber.  

## Software Store Return Policy

All purchases made through the Showit Store ([https://store.showit.co](https://store.showit.co/)) are final and no returns are offered at this time due to the nature of the digital download distribution method. If you have a specific question regarding your software please email [help@showit.co](mailto:help@showit.co).

## Showit Subscription Cancellation Policy

Subscription payments are paid for each month or year in advance. You can cancel at any time and your subscription will remain active through the end of current the billing cycle.

For subscription questions or problems (including requests for refunds) send an email to help@showitfast.com with information about your account. Upon receipt of your request one of our support team members will contact you with 2 business days.

## Security Policy

You can purchase from Showit, Inc. online with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to offer safe and secure credit card and electronic check transactions for our customers. The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card and electronic check processing networks (see an online payments diagram). The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including:

128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard. For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.Net Privacy Policy.

## Free Account Policy

Showit, Inc. does not allow the practice of masking domain names for Showit FREE and reserves the right to suspend or terminate any subscription masking a Vanity URL.

## Purchase Policy

Purchases through the Showit website software will be charged to the credit card provided during the subscription payment wizard inside Showit. Once approved you will receive an email confirmation detailing the amount of your one-time purchase, automatic monthly billing, or automatic yearly billing charge.

Showit reserves the right to charge additional fees to users who use more than amounts allocated for a Showit subscription (currently for Showit this is 10 gigabytes of disk space and/or more than 100 gigabytes of bandwidth per month).

Purchasing software and music licenses through store.showit.co can be done by entering your credit card information.

## Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

## Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

## Collection of Information

Non-Personal Information May include the user's operating system (Windows or Mac), type of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox), IP address, monitor screen resolution and color depth, referring pages, and frequency of visits. This information is used to analyze how visitors browse the site in order to make future improvements.

Personal Information Personal information collected from users of Showitfast.com may include first and last name, phone number, physical address, email address, comments, and permission from the user to add him/her to our mailing list. All personal information remains private within Showit, Inc. and is not distributed or sold to any outside organizations.

At Showit, Inc. your credit card and private information is not sold or shared with any third party and is used exclusively for your purchase at this site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Privacy Policy
